# Caitlin Chan

### **Administrative and Operations Professional**

**Address** Los Angeles, CA 90034 **Phone** 323-944-2062

E-mail caitlingchan@gmail.com

**LinkedIn** www.linkedin.com/in/caitlin-g-chan

Administrative Assistant with over 3 years of experience in fast-paced office settings, including real estate and entertainment. Hardworking team-player with expertise completing various clerical tasks and offering staff support. Responsible, punctual and productive professional looking to grow her career and use her passion to help people.

#### Skills

- Office Administration
- Office Operations
- Customer Service

- Project & Event Management
- Organization & Efficiency
- Written & Verbal Communication

### Work History

### Oct 2019 – May 2020

### **Administrative Assistant, West LA Region**

Caruso, Los Angeles, CA

- Assisted management with daily operational tasks for five properties, including The Grove
- Managed calendar, coordinated meetings and appointments for property GM and AGM
- Prepared and distributed various tenant letters and property memos
- Assisted in preparing annual budget, monthly financial forecasts, operations reports
- Served as liaison between 150+ property employees, tenants and management
- Executed large events, including Tree Lighting for 5,000+ attendees and the mayor of LA

#### Aug 2018 – Oct 2019

# Receptionist & Corporate Concierge Ambassador

Caruso, Los Angeles, CA

- Provided executives and employees with a unique concierge service experience
- Fulfilled daily service requests for 100+ corporate employees efficiently and accurately
- Greeted guests and notified internal employees of their arrival, answered phones and directed accordingly
- Facilitated office events and employee engagement activities
- Organized weekly breakfast and lunch program for corporate office

#### Jan 2018 – June 2018

# **Operations Intern**

House of Blues, Live Nation Entertainment, Hollywood, CA

- Assisted EVP, F&B Director, and Operations Coordinator, overseeing 11 HoB nationwide
- Updated weekly event calendars and assisted with new menu roll-outs to venues
- Managed weekly projects and conducted research as necessary
- Generated reports on online social media reviews through Reputology

#### June 2017 – Jan 2018

# **Event Planning Assistant & Personal Assistant**

Girl Friday Personal Assistant Services, South Pasadena, CA

- Responsible for meeting client requirements and successful event execution
- Organized facilities, décor, catering, entertainment, and day of event logistics
- Ran personal errands for clients including medication pick-up, grocery shopping, etc.

#### **Education**

#### Sept 2014 – June 2018

# **Bachelor of Science: Hospitality Management & Marketing**

California State Polytechnic University, Pomona - Pomona, CA

Minored in Marketing Management

Graduated with 3.64 GPA